# Quan Le

Highbury, Wellington | Mobile: 021 052 4016 | <a href="mailto:quanlenz1998@gmail.com">quanlenz1998@gmail.com</a> Portfolio: <a href="mailto:http://quanle-personal.com/">http://quanle-personal.com/</a>

# **Objective**

I am a Victoria University of Wellington graduate who has recently completed studies in a bachelor's degree in Computer Science. I am enthusiastic about utilizing my developer and interpersonal skills and in a Software Developer role or similar, to help me further develop these skills in the tech field, along with enhancing my experience in a practical and professional environment.

#### Education

## BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | 2016-2018 | VICTORIA UNIVERSITY OF WELLINGTON

- · Major: Computer Science
- · Grade Average: B+ Level
- Related coursework: Use of software engineering principles, theories and design, along with programming languages to develop software.

## **WELLINGTON COLLEGE | 2013-2016**

- · Related coursework: Math, Physics, Chemistry, Accounting, Web Design, Digital Technologies
- · Year 13 Endorsement of Excellence, Year 12 Endorsement of Merit

## **Skills & Abilities**

## **Programming Languages**

JavaScript, NodeJS, SQL, Java, C, HTML, CSS, JSX, C Sharp, Typescript, Swift.

#### **Tools**

React, Angular JS, Ionic, React Native, Amazon Web Services, Gradle, Google Firebase, Heroku, PostgreSQL, Microsoft Office suite, Windows Active Directory, Git & GitHub, Unity3D, Tosca Test Suite, XCode.

## Industry Knowledge

Data Structures and Algorithms, RESTful API, Web development Frameworks, Cloud Platforms, Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning, Software Development Life Cycle, Agile and DevOps, Project Management, Game Design, Software Testing and Automation, UX Design, Full-Stack Development, Databases.

#### Other transferable skills

- · Assembly and disassembly of a desktop PC and other consumer hardware.
- · A team-player who can efficiently perform cooperative tasks and communicate efficiently in a high-pressure team environment.
- An experienced leader who is capable of delegating responsibilities and mentor lesser experienced members of staff.
- · A level-headed problem-solver that can execute tasks in a strategic and innovative manner.
- · Strong interpersonal and customer-service skills, both verbally and written.

# **Experience**

## WAITER & BARISTA | WHERE'S CHARLIE | JULY 2018 - PRESENT

• Responsibilities: Providing customer services, handling financial transactions and payments, stock taking, schedule dining reservations, making beverages and coffees, mentoring new staff-members.

# JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | TWENTYTWO PROPERTY ADVISERS | MARCH 2018 – NOVEMBER 2018

• Responsibilities: Took part in a full-stack development role using NodeJS, PostgreSQL, Angular, Swift and deployed on the Heroku cloud platform as part of a year-long university project in collaboration with real external clients. Git and the Agile framework were also used to aid in project management.

# KITCHENHAND | MAC'S BREWBAR | JANUARY 2016 - JULY 2018

• Responsibilities: Maintaining workflow within the kitchen environment, assisting with food preparation, mentoring new staff-members.

## GROCERY ASSISTANT | NEW WORLD | NOVEMBER 2014 - JANUARY 2015

· Responsibilities: Managing and handling stock within a retail environment, providing customer support

## Personal

- · Fluent speaker in English and Vietnamese.
- Member of the International Students Association (Wellington College 2014-2015)
- · Wellington Social Football (2015)
- · Active guitar player

#### References

## MATTHEW ROGERS - SENIOR ADVISER - TWENTYTWO PROPERTY ADVISORS

· Phone number: 027 308 6247

• Email: matthew@twentytwo.co.nz

### KHEM SUNSET - HEADCHEF - MAC'S BREWBAR

Phone number: 020 400 72408Email: chef@macsbrewbar.co.nz

### ERICSON C. ITABLE - GENERAL MANAGER - WHERE'S CHARLIE RESTAURANT

Phone number: 021 027 12959Email: erson\_1231@yahoo.com